林德潤 TeJun Lin

soar.lin@gmail.com

0910-387-918

4F., No. 111-15, Fuxing Rd., Luzhou Dist., New Taipei City 24744, Taiwan (R.O.C)

Experienced developer with extensive server-side web development knowledge gathered across 10+ years in the industry. Well-versed in Front-End development. Designed and developed 4 completed web applications from use cases and functional requirements. Seeking to further improve HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript skills as the future frontend developer.

Experience

CommScope ARRIS Ruckus, Staff software Engineer - 2019/10 - Present

- Maintained system operation and ensure that P1 bugs can be diagnosed within 24 hours and eliminated within 72 hours.
- Developed new features based on PLM requirements in collaboration with UX.

Zoek Inc., Senior engineer - 2017/05 - 2019/10

- Built a responsive design website using the PHP slim framework, and use SPA (Single-page application) to create the transaction page increased user experience.
- Improved the transaction flow by using website analysis tools that reduced bounce rate by 13% (GA, FB pixel, hotjar)
- Introduced LINE Pay and Apply Pay in original credit card transactions that increase the transaction success rate by 6%
- Design and implement Restful API in Golang and created a customer management website by using Vue.js 2.x
- Established product sales time by using ElasticSearch and schedule calculations through AWS Lambda
- Use FCM (firebase cloud message) to establish a web push notification mechanism

Sagacity Technology Co., Ltd., Software engineer – 2013/04 - 2014/07, 2015/07 - 2017/02

- Led a team of 3 engineers and a designer to create a web application and mobile app
- Built a development and test environment platform on AWS.
- Introduced front-end automation process using Gulp that speeds up front-end development
- Designed and developed the question editing interface with React.js
- Developed the PDF / Word file upload question transpose tool with Vue.js 1.x and boosted the efficiency of data establishment around 80%

EATME Catering Consulting Co., Ltd., Product Manager - 2014/07 - 2015/06

- United designer and engineers as a small team to brainstorm EatMe App and running project with scrum
- Create Eatme official website with Laravel 4.2 and build a blog system including front-end display and back-end management
 - Integrate third-party payment API to sell EatMe Cards
- Create a landing page to display product features

Compal Electronics, Inc., Design Leader - 2011/08 - 2013/04

Porting audio function on android. Design IPC (Inter-Process Communication) mechanism for transformer pad project and demo at Computex 2012.

Academia Sinica, Software Engineer - 2007/01 - 2011/07

Digital archive system and Unencoded Chinese Character technology application development.

- Text source evolution (文字源演變), electronic stamp (電子圖章), e-card (電子賀卡) technology license to IQChinese Corp.
- Chinese character query (漢字查詢), e-card (電子賀卡) technology authorized to the WingNet Technology Co., Ltd.

Education

National Chung Cheng University - Master of Computer Science and Information Engineering, September 2004 - June 2006

Skills

Professional Skills

- Expert : Git, JavaScript, Pub, Sass, Vue.js
- Proficient : Angular, Ext.js, Webpack, Gulp, GA, SEO
- Intermediate: LAMP, PHP, Golang, ElasticSearch, Node.js, React.js, AWS

Personal Skills

 Problem Solving, Team Player, Communication, Collaboration, Time Keeping, Adaptability, Conflict Resolution

Reference

GitHub: https://github.com/soarlin Blog: https://soarlin.github.io/

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/soarlin/